<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Oliviabeauty]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Oliviabeauty]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/oliviabeauty/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 05:55:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/oliviabeauty/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Eliminating Acne Scars
Luckily, there are several things you can do to be rid of them. There are two basic types of acne ‘scars’ I will discuss. The dark spots that remain after an acne breakout are known as post-inflammatory hyperpigmentation (PIH). Those marks are very common. However, while they may take a long time to heal, those annoying discolored spots will fade away eventually. Certain ethnicities, such as people of Asian descent, African descent, or people with darker skin tones in general seem to be more prone to PIH marks lasting longer than are people of Caucasian decent or people with lighter skin tones. Exfoliation will help these marks to be gone faster. If you would like to speed up the healing process of dark spots, drugstores sell "brightening" creams containing kojic acid. Kojic acid functions primarily as a skin-lightening agent. 
Another form of discoloration treatment is to use stronger formulas by a dermatologist containing an ingredient called tretinoin. Both over-the-counter products and prescription products containing tretinoin (retinol) can fade discolored marks over time and prevent future ones. 
Many "lightening" or "whitening" or "bleaching" creams contain dangerous ingredients, including mercury or hydroquinone. The harm caused by these ingredients has now changed the description of these products: the creams are now referred to as "brightening" creams. It seems odd to me that changing a single word makes something "safe", but I guess it's how people can stay out of trouble with a technicality. 
The other form of scarring makes up indented lesions or bumps on the skin and is a more severe form of scarring. For this uneven texture, you can try a drugstore product containing alpha hydroxy acids to smoothen your skin over time. For quicker results, you can visit a dermatologist who can fix the problem with lasers, chemical peels, injectable fillers, or other exfoliating procedures. 
The least expensive and most effective way to improve your skin's texture is to exfoliate your skin yourself at home. If you are responsible and make exfoliating a routine, you will see great results. How frequently you exfoliate will depend solely on you and it’s different for everyone. Personally, I exfoliate every day, but it's what my skin needs. You might need it once a day or you might only need it once a week, but either way, removing that layer of dead skin cells is imperative. 
Ready for the annoying part? Yes, we've all heard it before: do NOT pick at your pimples. They're more likely to scar if you do.
</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/oliviabeauty/92fb5b7e-bfdd-4bf5-a5dd-f17fbbeb1e53/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">92fb5b7e-bfdd-4bf5-a5dd-f17fbbeb1e53</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 05:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6becf620-1069-4606-8a08-e8fa696e1918.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/oliviabeauty/5a1727b3-0dce-40dc-8a25-60f341be68d9/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">5a1727b3-0dce-40dc-8a25-60f341be68d9</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 05:09:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>